

I'm a quick learner who loves solving puzzles and being of service.

My foundation in IT began as a Field Technician during the pandemic. This has been a trying time for our community, and it was a challenge and an honor to serve as an essential worker.

I'm proud to continue serving my community in my current position at Contra Costa Health, where I collaborate with several IT departments in providing support to our hospitals and clinics.

I'm also attending school full-time on my way to my degree in Computer Science and have a special interest in SQL and Python programming, disaster recovery, and security.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 209-402-1056

EMAIL:

calbreathian@gmail.com

### **HOBBIES**

Guitar
Drawing
Weightlifting
Videogaming

#### **SOFTWARE**

Windows - Linux - Mac Office - WinSCP - PuTTY Access - SSMS - DBeaver Active Directory - PagerDuty vSphere - HEAT - IGEL UMS Citrix DaaS - Epic - RightFax

# IAN CALBREATH

I.T. PROFESSIONAL

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Los Medanos College | Diablo Valley College

2023 - Current

Computer Science major graduating in Spring '25 with 4.0 GPA. Alongside my core curriculum, I have completed specific courses on SQL, Python, security applications, and network configurations.

#### Modesto Junior College

2020 - 2021

PC Servicing and Repair courses with preparation for the CompTIA A+ exam. After completing this coursework I passed the CompTIA A+ exam, earning my first certificate.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Contra Costa County Health Services - Computer Operator II 2022 - Current

- Collaborated cross-functionally with Database, Service Desk, and Infrastructure teams to expedite resolution of after-hours issues with support calls, automated jobs, infrastructure downtime, and catastrophic system failures.
- Acted as Service Desk support agent during evening hours to ensure uninterrupted support for critical healthcare facilities.
- Reduced mean incident resolution time by 35% by implementing incident management policies.
- Ensured Disaster Recovery readiness by creating daily environment backups.
- Misc. duties such as: Facilitate file transfers, monitor SQL Agent jobs for completion and errors, batch scan files for errors, monitor system health interfaces, VMware connections, cluster health, and CCTV systems.

## PAQ Inc. dba Food 4 Less - IT Field Technician 2020 - 2021

- Ensured store operability by supporting helpdesk calls, visiting store sites daily to check in with store director and manager, and servicing IT equipment.
- Organized PIN Pad repair/replacement into one streamlined process and established line of communication with vendor that was not present before.
- Organized vendor appointments with stores for services we could not complete in-house such as running electrical lines, satellite installation, and Point-of-Sale system installation.

## **Appen Global – Content Evaluator** 2018 – 2019

 Maintained a high level of professionalism and empathy while analyzing search result and website content to determine if content is harmful to users.